

About Me

Student who recently graduated with a professional degree in Logistics and Transport with a **2-month** internship as a Logistics assistant and **2-years** as a sales manager of cash operations and inventory and order tracking.

I have a great sense of organization and solid knowledge.

I know how to integrate without difficulty into new work contexts thanks to a real team spirit and excellent listening and communication skills.

Education

Bachelor's Degree: Professional Study in Logistics and Transport

Polydisciplinary Faculty of Larache

2021 – 2024

Skill

Grit & Resilience
Attention to detail / accuracy
Office automation
Growth mindset
Time management



Formation

Virtual Assistance

African Leadership ALX

Computer Science

Pathway Program

DATA ACADEMIE

African Leadership ALX

Experience

Dirafrost Maroc

2024

Logistics assistant

- Preparing shipments by packaging orders, labeling parcels, and organizing delivery documentation
- Resolving delivery issues and assisting with logistical problem-solving to prevent delays

Benta Progress SARL | 2022 - 2024)

Sales

- Engaging with customers to understand needs and recommend appropriate products or services
- Coordinating with other departments (logistics, customer service, etc.) to ensure smooth post-sale processes

Hult Prize

2024 - Present)

Élémentaire

Logistics & Operations Manager

 Overseeing logistics and operational planning for club events, workshops, and pitch competitions

Languages

Spanish

Arabic | Maternelle
English | Advancé
French | Courant

	Contact
0	+212 682 497 699
O	Saidlara351@gmail.com
0	N° 15 AV Zalaka Residence Nakhil-LARACHE
	Said Bentahra
апнив	Saidzzzz